Charles R. Martin Photographs, 1945-2011 AIS.2012.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, 1945-1998; II.
  - 35mm Negatives, 1.
    - 1974
      - Health Research & Services Foundation, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - United Way- Mt. Lebanon Volunteers, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Market Square- Tom & German Band, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - M-3- Misc., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - United Way- Mt. Wade Volunteers, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Health Research & Services Foundation- Monroeville Mall, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Personal, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 18-19, 33, 35)
      - United Way, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - United Way- Shaler Jr. High School, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - United Way- Child Guidance Center, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 22-23, 25)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 24, 26-27)
      - Point Fountain & Buildings in Fog, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Personal- Cat on Benz, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Berkman, Yoder & Spay, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Shady Side Academy, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 31-32)
      - Shady Side Academy- Slide copy, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - 1975
      Subjects include Goodwill; United Fund; Girl Scouts; ICM School of Business; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Buhl Science Center; University Club; Carnegie Mellon University; and United Way (Pittsburgh Steelers). Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Harry & Timmy (Zerite) Jones- Deep Creek, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Personal- Evans City Passenger Station- Misc., 1975 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Krawley – Diamond Ring, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - University Club, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 39-46)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 47-53)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
      - Ping Pong, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7-9)
      - University Club- Seals & Dice Slide Copy, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - University Club, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 11, 18, 21, 23-24, 36, 39, 42-44)
      - Shady Side Academy, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 12-14)
      - Scaife Art Museum, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 15, 20)
      - University Club- Dinner Meeting, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - ECAC Swim Meet, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Personal, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Snow, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - University Club- Meeting, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 25, 46-48)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 26-33, 37-38)
      - American Bridge, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 34-35, 49-52)
      - Copy Work for Dr. Lewis, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Health Research and Service Foundation, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - North Hills Bike Club, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - American Bridge, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1-4, 12-14, 42-44)
      - University Club, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5-11, 15, 17-18, 20, 41)
      - H.V. Nicholson Reunion, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Shady Side Academy- Report Meeting at Duquesne Club, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Dowty Corporation- Cranberry Industrial Park, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Dowty Corporation, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 23-25, 56)
      - Personal- Stoughton Lake, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Allan #1, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Allan #2, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Allan #3, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 30-36, 38-40)
      - Personal- Mae- Bike Race (club), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Yough Reservoir, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Shady Side Academy- Charter Signatures, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Mexico '75, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 46-50)
      - Nikon "F" Test, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 51)
      - Carnegie Mellon University- Bike Races, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 52-55)
      - United Way, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1-2, 5-10, 21, 27, 38-42)
      - Windwood Swim Team, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Mrs. Mehan- Passports, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - ICM, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11-13)
      - ICM- Cleveland, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
      - University Club- Meeting, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 17-19, 28-29, 33-37, 44-45)
      - United Way Meeting- & Mr. Chandler, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Haberstyob- Passports, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - United Way- Ambassador Group, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - United Way- at Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - United Way- Lemmington Home for the Aged, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 25-26)
      - United Way- Steelers, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Ocracoke, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Emily Buks, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Personal- M-3 Summicron, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Personal- Leica III Summar, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 46)
      - United Way- Cocktail Party, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 47)
      - United Way- at PNB Cocktail Party, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - Personal- Sal & Kit- Booth at Craft Show- Pitt, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - 1976
      Subjects include United Way; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Salvation Army; Bradford Woods School; President Gerald R. Ford's visit to the Republican Committee of Southwest Pennsylvania; Carnegie Mellon University Bike Race; Shadyside Academy; Sweetwater Art Center (Sewickley, PA); Barkus Bakery; Lemmington Home; Ambassador to the UN-William Scranton; McConnells Mills; unidentified photographs.
      - Bette Roth, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 50-55)
      - Personal- Beaver Falls- December 1975, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Barkus Bakery, Rt. 8, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3, 15-19)
      - N 40 & Kit, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Kit, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - United Way- Mr. UNK, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7-14)
      - Keith Swanson, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - United Way- G. Harton Singer III, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Dowty Corporation, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Swenson, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 23-27, 37, 45-49)
      - Yorktown Properties – Beckman, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Yorktown- Wyoming, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 29-36)
      - North Allegheny Swim Team, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - Yorktown Properties- Bagdad, Arizona, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 39-40)
      - Boro of Bradford Woods, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 41)
      - Maple Sugaring, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 42)
      - Yorktown Properties, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 43)
      - Personal- French Intensive Garden, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 44)
      - Leica III Test, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 50)
      - Personal- Kit & Rabbits, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - Bradford Woods School, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 52-53)
      - Bradford Woods School, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1-2, 6-9)
      - Glenn Kress – Bldr, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
      - United Way- Awards at Federal Employees Luncheon, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
      - United Way- Stouffers Meeting, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 13-14, 17-22, 28-33)
      - Personal- IIIA Elmar, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Personal, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - United Way- Loudin Twins- Cerebral Palsy Center, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 23-24)
      - United Way- Maggie Blakely- Lemmington Home for the Aged, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - United Way- Hill House, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Phil Duncan- Office Personnel, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 28-33)
      - Beckman- Copy Work from Slides, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Copy work, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Turek & Heller- for Mr. McGovern, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - United Way- A.R.P. Meeting, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - United Way- Myasthenia Gravis-Tony Randall Visit, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - Sweetwater Art Center, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Pittsburgh Speech & Hearing Society, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 40-41)
      - Salvation Army, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 42-44)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 45-52)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1-11)
      - Shady Side Academy, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 12-16)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children & Tonis Graduation, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Media Graphics, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 18-19)
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 20-25)
      - United Way- You've Got a Friend, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 26-29)
      - Sun Oil Co.- Bill Torden, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Diner, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Job No. F- Portrait Pictures, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Job No. E- Classroom Setting, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Offices, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Job No. D- Computer Data Center, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Job No. C- Offices, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - Job No. B- Offices, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Job No. A., Offices/ Typing, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Personal- Leica IIIA Summer, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Carnegie Mellon University- Bike Race, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 40-45)
      - Carnegie Mellon University- Bike Race and Shadyside Art-Craft Show, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - Personal- Verna Mae Slone – KY & Ocracoke, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Personal- Bybee Pottery & Verna Mae Slone-KY, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 48)
      - Personal- National Bike Race- Bybee Pottery KY, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - National Bike Race – KY, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 50-51)
      - United Way- Delores Williams- Allegheny Ludlum, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 52)
      - United Way- Levinson, Goldman & Team Captains/ Andy Russell, Tape session w/ Marshall and Levinson, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - McConnells Mills, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Personal- OM-1 Test, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - United Way- Vocational Rehabilitation Center Tour, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 4-5, 7)
      - United Way- Executive Meeting, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - United Way- Loaned Executive Meeting, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - United Way- Loaned Executive Hill House Tour, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - United Way- Bette Roth, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Personal- 24mm Lens Test, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Personal- Test, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Shady Side Academy, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - United Way- Lemmington Home for the Aged, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 14-15)
      - Lemmington Home for the Aged, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Personal- Bederman Copies, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - United Way- Health- O- Rama- Eastland Mall, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 18-19)
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 21-22, 31-32)
      - Personal, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 23, 25-26, 35, 37-38)
      - United Way- Meeting at Oakmont Elks, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Kess Builders, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Republican Convention - Southwest Pennsylvania – President Ford's Visit, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 28-29)
      - Personal- Ambassador to UN William Scranton, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 30)
      - Personal- Hartwood Acres for Joe White, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 33)
      - United Way- Thank you Party- William Penn, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 34, 36)
      - Karen Swenson Copies, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - 1977
      Subjects include Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Arthritis Foundation; United Way; Sweetwater Art Center; Salvation Army; Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); Elks Club; Sewickley Arts Festival; Pittsburgh Blind Association. Also includes Martin's camera test images.
      - Lee Norse, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 40-45, 47-48)
      - Personal- Penn State vs. Pitt- Swim Meet, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 46)
      - Peter Eckrich & Sons, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 49)
      - Lernberger Passports, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 50)
      - United Way- Press Club Awards Luncheon- P.R.S.A., 1977 (Box 45, Folder 51)
      - Fowler Homestead, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 52)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - United Way- Retake of Salvation Army Presentation- from PRSA, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Personal- Big Daddy & Nanook (Hooke's Dog), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - United Way- Big Brother, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
      - United Way- Ester Abbes Passports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Duncan & Jagnese Maurice, Mae, Sal & Self- Passports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Passports- Carol Fritsche, & Spain Trip, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Personal, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 10, 19)
      - Elks, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 11-12)
      - Personal- Schmautz & Big Daddy, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Health Research and Service Foundation, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Personal- And Holman Res. Exterior, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - MacDonald- Dr. Holman Res., 1977 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 17-18, 20)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten and Rafferty Passports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Rathke & Kitty Passports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Personal- Mac- P.R. Pics, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Salvation Army- Meeting, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 25-28)
      - Personal- M-3 Test, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - Koppers Co.- E. Brady & Bruin, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - Personal- Sweetwater Clan, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - United Way, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 32-37, 51)
      - The Yingling- Route 8 Bar, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 38)
      - United Way- Pittsburgh Hearing & Speech Society, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 39)
      - United Way- Multiple Sclerosis Clinic St. Francis and Pittsburgh Hearing & Speech Society, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 40)
      - United Way- Marg. Bymes w/Cathe Social Services Homemaker, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 41)
      - United Way- Abernathy Family (Red Cross), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 42)
      - Personal- M-3, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 43)
      - 3 River Arts Festival, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 44)
      - Sweetwater & Joe Bullick Passports, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 45)
      - Sweetwater, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 46-48)
      - DiGiacobbe, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 49)
      - United Way- Natrona Heights, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 50)
      - United Way- Multiple Sclerosis Clinic St. Francis Hospital, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 52)
      - United Way- Pittsburgh Hearing & Speech Society, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - DiGiacobbe, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Personal- Dog, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - AMC- Personnel File Job, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Personal- Gretchen Straley, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - AMC & Personal, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Personal- Panorama atop Center, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - AMC- Reg. & Passports, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - United Way- Delores Wild, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - United Way- Blandee Stanton, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Personal- Spain, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 11-16)
      - United Way- J. Hyatt Hammond Associates- Awards Group, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - United Way- Health- O- Rama at Post Office, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - United Way- Health- O- Rama at Post Office-Ambassador at Hill House, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - United Way - Ambassadors at C.S. Services & Hill House, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - United Way- Awards at Hill House, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - United Way- Ambassadors at JHHA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Sewickley Arts Festival, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 23-27)
      - United Way- Fox Channel Meeting at Martha Home, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Black OM-1 Test, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Board Meeting, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 30-31)
      - Personal- OM-1 Test, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 33-41)
      - Dolly Badke Res., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - Personal- Winder Test, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 43)
      - TRBC (?), 1977 (Box 47, Folder 44-49)
      - R.E. Ludy & AMC (Dave Katasky), 1977 (Box 47, Folder 50)
      - Bikes N' Things, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 51-52)
      - Pifer, Jerry- Campaign Pictures for School Board, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - United Way- Labor Meeting, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Arthritis Foundation, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Arthritis Foundation- M-3 Test, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Luke- Snarcly Lumber (?), 1977 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Luke, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 6-13)
      - Personal- Family, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Copy of Kraus Contracts- VT, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Anastasia License & AMC (Larry White), 1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Yoder, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 17-18)
      - Car Damage Picture, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Head Shots, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - 1978
      Subjects include the Bradford Woods Kindergarten; United Way; Salvation Army; Community Services of Pittsburgh; Elks Meeting; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Ocracoke Island, North Carolina; Pittsburgh Blind Association (PBA); Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); McConnells Mills; Mellon Bank; United Way; Cross Country Skiing; unidentified images. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Scenic Images, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - United Way- Medtect, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 22-26, 28, 36)
      - Personal, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 27, 29, 31, 33, 35)
      - Personal- Corkey's Shop, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 30, 34)
      - Berger Brochure, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 37-40)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Personal- Wild Goose Chase, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Mac- Roller Ride- William Penn, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 43-47)
      - B/W Slides of Phil Berger Seismograph, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      - Personal- HP-5, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 49)
      - AMC & TX, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 50)
      - Cross Country Skiing- North Park, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 51-53)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 54-59)
      - Peter Eckrich Co.- Butler Foodland, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 60)
      - Cross Country Skiing, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3, 8, 10-12, 61-63)
      - Bradford Wood Church- Dr. Jerry Pifer, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 5-7)
      - Personal- OM-1, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Personal, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 13-14, 50)
      - Ocracoke, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Elks Meeting & Sewer Job, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Community Service of Pennsylvania, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17-21)
      - Personal- Antique Auto Show & Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Salvation Army, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
      - Salvation Army- Meeting, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 25-26)
      - Deer Lake Bike Race, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 27-29)
      - Highland Park Bike Race, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 30-34)
      - Duncan & Laqnese, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - United Way- Camp, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 36-37)
      - Kayak at McConnells Mills, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Copying of VT, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - Personal- McConnells Mills, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 40-41)
      - AMC, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 42)
      - Hugh Stubbs, Sound equip., AMC, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      - Valencia Lounge- Joe Yingling Legal Case, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - United Way- Poster Job, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 45-46)
      - United Way, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 47-49, 64-65)
      - Health Research & Services Foundation- Meditech trailer, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      - Health Research & Services Foundation, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 52-54, 56)
      - United Way Ambassador- Mellon Square, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 58-59)
      - Mac at Ross Jr. High, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 60)
      - United Way, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
      - United Way- Revlon -Bill Blass, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 6-9)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 10-11)
      - Personal- Mac Center Mall, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Mellon Bank, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 13-14)
    - 1979
      Subjects include Mellon Bank; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Sweetwater Art Center; Volkswagen.; Ocracoke Island, North Carolina; (TRBC); Three River Festival; Sterling Graphics; Warner BROS.; Salvation Army; Pittsburgh Blind Association. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and passport images taken for friends and family.
      - Tom w/ Martha Crouse before Prom, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Personal- Mac Roller Ride Northway Mall, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Personal, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 17-18, 63)
      - Mellon Bank- Dick James, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Copies of Firth Letters To Bert Smith- UCSF, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Terry Brusca Passports, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 22-27, 58-59, 61)
      - Personal- IIIa – Summar Test, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Tom- Folio pic & Sewer Line before landfill, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Sweetwater- Laura Turgem, Darcy Walick, Macy Squirs, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Liz Bjelland and Test, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Liz Bjelland, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 32-33)
      - United Way, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 34-35)
      - Personal- OM-1 Test, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Personal-OM-2 Scratch Test, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Personal- Old Negatives 1959 (?), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Salvation Army- Meeting, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 39-41)
      - United Way- Louise Child Care Center, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 42-43)
      - Personal- McConnells Mills, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Personal- Bike Races, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 45)
      - Tom and Martha, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 46-48)
      - Warner Bros.- Movie/ Bike Promo, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 49-50)
      - Sterling Graphics- Copy for Ad, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Bike Races – Joan Moudiale at Arts Festival, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Festival, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 53)
      - United Way- Meeting, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 54, 56)
      - Personal- 3 Rivers Arts Festival, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 55)
      - 3 River Festival, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 57, 60)
      - Local Bikers going to '79 Nationals, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 62)
      - Mellon Bank- Anna Eberle – Skeet Shooter State Champion, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 64)
      - Personal- McConnells Mills & Anna Eberle, Mellon Bank, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 65)
      - United Way, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 1-9, 31)
      - Parkvalle Shop- Balloon, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Duncan & Lagnese, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Biking- ACA TRBC, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Personal- OM 2 Test, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 13-14)
      - TRBC, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 15-17)
      - Ocracoke, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 18-24)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - United Way- Spec. Team, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 26-30)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 32-33)
      - Personal, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 34-36, 39)
      - Personal- Newark O., Dawes Arb., 1979 (Box 51, Folder 37-38)
      - School for the Blind, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 40-42)
      - Pennsylvania Blind Association, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 43-45)
      - Bell Passports/Visas, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 46)
      - Copy Job- Karen Sprague, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - 1980